paper-source.com 2019-02-09

# Security & Privacy | Paper Source

We know that you trust us with your personal information, and we take the privacy of our customers seriously. Your personal information is used for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, analyzing trends and statistics, informing you of our new products, services and offers, and providing you with information from and about Paper Source. In addition, we contract with marketing partners to help manage and optimize our web store and brand communications.

## Information Sharing

### Catalog

If you sign up to receive catalogs, information on workshops, projects, local information, new merchandise, store openings or other Paper Source news, we may rent, share, sell or exchange your information with certain third parties we believe may be of interest to you.

To opt out of receiving catalog mailings from Paper Source, please notify customer service. Allow 1-2 catalog cycles for processing.

### Email

When you subscribe to Paper Source emails you’ll receive regular communication regarding new merchandise, workshops, store openings and other Paper Source news. Your email address is never shared or sold to third parties.

To remove yourself from our email list, please notify customer service or click the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of any of our email messages.

### Additional Online

We contract with online companies to provide services that help manage and improve your customer experience, including shipping services, data management, promotional services, etc. We provide our service providers with the information needed for them to perform these services, and ask that these providers have privacy practices consistent with ours.

### Cookies

As a website visitor, small amounts of data are stored on your computer, which help us improve our site and make it easier for you to use. We never use cookies to save passwords, credit card numbers or other highly confidential information.

### Web Analytics

Our web analytics provider helps us assess visitation to our website by placing small pixel tags and cookies on our site. While this allows us to track visits and analyze our website traffic, the data retrieved cannot be used for any reason without our authorization.

To change your cookie status, please notify customer service. If you delete your cookies, use a different browser, or use a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out. Please allow time for processing.

We use a third-party provider to conduct surveys from time to time. You have the option to respond to this survey which helps us gather information on how well we met your expectations on purchase experience, product and delivery/package arrival. We do not share any customer information with this third-party provider. They may offer services to our customers and you are not obligated to engage in these services. These services are offered independently of Paper Source.

### Online Advertising

We contract with third-party service providers who help us place advertising messages on other websites. We may directly collect and these providers may also collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. This information may be used to target advertising messages to you based on your interests. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a cookie and pixel tag, which is an industry standard technology used by most major websites. Your personal information is not shared directly with these providers, as it is made anonymous by a vendor contracted with the provider before it reaches the provider's system. If you prefer not to receive relevant banner advertising from our third party service providers, please visit the NAI (Network Advertising Initiative) website, which allows opt-out for all of its members' cookies from a central opt-out page. [Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) to opt-out with NAI. To opt-out of direct enhanced online advertising provided by us, please notify customer service.

We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with relevant online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, [click here](http://dtmc.papersource.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=2389&cname=Paper%20Source&cmagic=063e26&clogo=2389.png&loc=us&lang=en-us).

If you would like to request your information not be included in our behavioral advertising practices, please notify customer service. If you delete your cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out. Please allow time for processing.

## Secure Shopping

This site uses a secure server (SSL) to encrypt all of your personal information. We use strong security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of your information once it is in our records.

Our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), which is encrypted and protected with the best encryption software in the industry—SSL. SSL is designed to render information unreadable should anyone try to intercept it. In addition, Paper Source _does not store credit card number information._ When ordering online, this information is sent directly to the authorizing banks.

_Please note_ : Email is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers. We will never ask for sensitive information via email.

## Privacy Policy Update

Paper Source reserves the right to change or modify this policy at any time by posting the revised policy on our website, effective immediately. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you purchase products from us or use our website.

### Questions

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact our customer service team.
